Why are you asking me
for six million?
I need six million
to keep a man
for three months.
Fine.
But remember this,
whether you keep a hundred,
a thousand,
or ten thousand men,
you, Liu Ruyan,
will always be my woman.
Ruyan.
I love you, Ruyan.
I'm the only one who truly loves you.
What are you doing?
Ruyan is my woman.
Do you think I'm blind?
She was never your woman.
She is mine.
What gives you the right?
Everything here is mine.
Just now,
I bought everything
that belongs to you.
What?
Aren't you just a security guard?
I am the first heir to Ousha Group,
Ouyang Tianyi.
I don't care who you are.
That kiss just now,
I want it back.
Okay.
The director is explaining the scene.
Quiet.
Director.
Mr. Heying,
you truly are the long-time pillar of the musical theater troupe.
I'm flattered.
Your expressions,
the feel,
were absolutely wonderful.
I'm flattered.
That's why,
spending so many years in the musical theater troupe
was really a waste of your talent.
It held you back.
What is a real actor?
This is a real actor.
Impressive.
So the short drama track
is the most suitable for you.
But there's just one thing.
It's slightly lacking a bit of...
Passion.
Hold on.
What should you do?
You love this woman very much.
You need to feel her in every way.
Do you understand?
Director.
And you.
When you kiss,
you must fully commit.
Right.
Then feel her body temperature,
and her breath.
What do you mean you couldn't stop him?
Take a look at the contract first.
Playing the male lead, Ning Caichen.
Yes.
In all the dramas we signed with him before,
he was guaranteed the male lead in every one,
and always as the primary lead.
It's my fault this time.
In order to sign Jin Xi,
I completely
forgot about this.
I even forgot to update the contract.
Therefore,
we breached the contract first.
It's understandable that Heying left.
But he shouldn't have just left without discussing it with me.
What do we do now?
Don't we have two understudies for this play?
We must get through this audition first no matter what.
If you really can't stop worrying about Jinxi,
we still have time to find two understudies.
Are you crazy?
Are you really going to give up on Top Music Avenue,
this S-tier music variety show?
Brother Jianshe just left.
I can't ask for any more leave.
Just because he left,
they definitely have to interview new actors.
That's why you have a chance to ask for leave.
I can't go.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
It's just a matter of me talking to Wu.
No.
Do you know how rare this show is?
Fine.
I got up early just to accompany you to the interview,
I didn't even attend Tiaotiao's sports meet.
I'm sorry,
Hu.
In order to meet the standard
of a real musical actor,
I can't be half-hearted at this stage.
In that case,
bye.
I'm going to Tiaotiao's sports meet.
Are you just going to leave us here?
At least drop us off at the rehearsal room.
No.
Sister Hu.
Let's go, brother.
Let's get a taxi at the intersection.
So handsome.
After crossing a thousand mountains,
into the bright lights.
Your ties
follow like a shadow.
This is why
Mr. Qingsong is only suited to be a choreographer.
Eventually crossing the mountains,
waiting until now.
Stop laughing.
Light clouds and gentle breeze.
Pour more wine.
Is there still no news of Mr. Heying recently?
No.
Then how about we check the places he usually goes?
The last time he came for training
was probably last week.
Last week.
Some director named Zha came to see him then.
Director Zha came?
They seemed to be discussing shooting a short drama.
Short drama?
What short drama?
Those mini-app short dramas.
They're pretty good.
Like 'Dragon King Son-in-law',
'Rebirth of the Soldier King',
'Boss Falls for the Nanny',
and 'Rebirth and Counterattack'.
They are really good.
Sir, just swipe your card.
All right, go ahead.
Mr. Heying.
They said you went to act in a short drama.
Do not stand in my way.
Mr. Heying.
Why did you go to act in a short drama?
I don't need to explain my affairs to anyone.
Then...
Are you going to ignore us and the theater troupe?
I said,
don't ask anymore.
I am sorry.
Some things
are destined not to be repeated.
Mr. Heying,
you sound weird talking like this.
Are you telling me what to do?
Yes,
the director sent me to find you.
Tell the director
I won't be going back for a while.
Why?
I said stop asking.
Mr. Heying,
if you don't tell me why,
I won't leave.
Feel your breath.
Stay if you want.
But for now,
relax.
I'm going to my yoga class.
New students, please take a seat.
Director.
Eating?
Let me see.
It's the scene with Nie Xiaoqian and Ning Caichen.
I feel like
the atmosphere here
could be built up a bit more.
The atmosphere is already there with the music.
Is it missing some
physical movements to increase their intimacy?
Physical movements?
Like what?
For example,
holding hands tightly.
Or
Ning Caichen gently stroking Nie Xiaoqian's hair.
No,
that's not what I meant.
Stop talking.
You're straying too far.
I really didn't mean that.
I figured it out after what happened last time.
I need to respect you.
From now until the end of this play,
we will just maintain the distance of an actor and a director.
Don't worry.
Director.
How is it?
Any news about Heying?
He went with Charlie Wang to shoot short dramas.
Why is it this guy again?
He seems serious this time.
I thought he was just
being emotional because of what Sister Hu said.
Why would he go shoot short dramas?
He said
short dramas suit him better than musicals right now.
But I know
this isn't how he really feels.
Jinxi.
I'll be blunt.
Ever since you came,
Mr. Heying has been very anxious.
He feels he has lost his sense of presence and validation in the troupe.
Mr. Heying,
you haven't left yet?
Xiao Qi.
How long has it been since you joined the troupe?
Since I graduated,
it's been almost a year of interning.
Is that so?
Since the first time I performed in a musical,
it's been ten years.
I remember
the first play I saw at the troupe
was Mr. Heying's "Cailou Ji".
That was the director's first time adapting a traditional play.
As the lead actor, you were truly radiant,
and the center of attention.
Now I'm washed up,
and completely ignored.
How could that be?
You are still radiant now.
It's just that Jin Xi took your lead role.
The director is strict with him,
so he pays a little less attention to you.
Jin Xi likes to joke around.
Everyone prefers laughing with him,
so they interact with you a little less.
Putting all that aside,
you are still the pillar of our troupe.
what else do I have left?
The fan incident
is exactly
the fuse for his inferiority and anxiety.
Jianshe would think of me this way.
Where is he? I'll go find him now.
No.
I don't believe Jianshe would think of me this way.
Xiao Qi.
Wait until the weekend.
We will bring Jianshe back together.
Okay.
Three years.
Three whole years.
Three years ago today.
You forced me.
You forced me to enter on my knees.
Now I want the entire Su family
to kneel and watch me leave.
If you're weak, even breathing is wrong.
Even breathing is wrong.
Du Heying.
You are actually acting in short dramas.
Hello, may I ask who you are?
I've been a fan of yours for years,
silently supporting you.
To restore your artistic dignity,
I didn't hesitate to target
Jin Xi, who took away your artistic crown.
But you've willingly stooped so low,
abandoning noble musicals
to become a slave to short dramas.
So you are that fan of mine.
Did you hit Jin Xi?
Today,
I officially announce that I am no longer your fan.
For the rest of my life,
I will treat the name Du Heying like dog shit.
Don't go!
Short dramas are also a popular art form
loved by the people!
I want you to watch.
Ruyan.
You are clean.
I want you to have my baby.
I am willing.
Kiss her.
Wait a minute.
Sorry, director.
Let's stop for a moment.
What's wrong,
Mr. Jianshe?
Director,
well,
I just thought about it.
That,
that line,
is it a bit disrespectful to women?
That line
is disrespectful to women, right?
Yes.
Are you the screenwriter?
Are you the director?
On this set,
only I can call cut.
Do you understand?
Understood, director.
How many scenes left?
Sixty-three scenes, director.
More than sixty scenes.
Will you take responsibility if we can't finish?
Sorry, director.
I can't hear you.
Louder.
Aren't you a stage actor?
Sorry, director!
Lunch break!
What a jerk.
Don't be mad, director.
Don't cast musical actors anymore.
Mr. Heying.
The director said you can get lost.
He deleted your scenes for the afternoon.
Mr. Heying.
Jianshe.
Jianshe, wait for me.
Jinxi.
Stop chasing me.
Jianshe, you can't quit the troupe.
I'm getting old.
The troupe doesn't need me anymore.
Jianshe, are you kidding?
You are the star.
Jinxi, you are performing better and better.
There is no place for me in the troupe anymore.
My progress is all because of you.
You taught me acting and singing.
You also taught me what a good musical actor is.
I told you I'm old.
Can you not take such big steps?
Your legs are longer than mine.
You two.
Wait ten seconds before chasing me.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Mr. Heying.
Jianshe.
I know where Mr. Heying lives.
I'll call a cab.
Okay.
Mr. Heying.
Jianshe.
Wait for us.
Mr. Heying.
Jianshe.
Stop chasing me.
I won't go back with you.
Mr. Heying.
The troupe really needs you.
Please go back with us.
Mr. Heying.
This is not me.
What's wrong with you?
Jinxi.
Think of a way quickly.
Jianshe.
Mr. Heying!
Can you please stop shouting?
I will not go back with you.
Mr. Heying!
Open the door!
I'm begging you.
Mr. Heying!
Stop shouting.
It's useless to shout here.
Isn't this his balcony?
He can definitely hear us from here.
Are you a human or a ghost?
You don't need to waste your breath.
No matter what you say today,
I won't go back.
Mr. Heying.
If you don't go back,
we won't leave here either.
Mr. Heying,
please come back.
Xiaoqi,
can you stop making a scene?
You summed it up perfectly the other day.
After so many years in the musical theater circle,
I've gone from being a pretty good leading man
to this state.
I lost my leading roles.
I lost the director's attention.
I lost the attention of my troupe members.
What else do I have left?
I only have one loyal fan left,
and it turns out she's a
nightmare that has been haunting us.
What face do I have to stay?
What's the point of staying?
But
do you really think
filming short dramas suits you?
Does it matter if it suits me?
It's just the beginning.
There's always a process.
I signed a ten-drama long-term contract with Charlie Wang.
I don't have to worry about not having dramas to film.
Jianshe,
do you really feel happy filming short dramas?
Whether I'm happy or not,
is it really that important?
Then what is important?
Are musicals no longer important to you?
Musicals will always be important to me.
It's just that now,
I'm no longer important to musicals.
Jinxi.
Actually, after spending so much time together,
I've long stopped resenting you for taking my lead role.
I have to admit,
you are younger,
better,
and have more potential than me.
The future of musicals
should belong to actors like you.
And now,
I'm no longer fit to play the male lead.
Whether it's our A Chinese Ghost Story
or the musical stage,
I'm no longer an indispensable role.
I might as well start doing something else.
Maybe I'll do better in film and TV
than you.
My mind is made up.
You should go back.
Jinxi.
In that case,
don't blame me.
Jianshe.
You have no future shooting short dramas with Charlie Wang.
It was you and Ning Jin
who made me realize
how terrible my previous acting was.
Jianshe.
Look,
this is 'Huayue Zhuan' directed by Charlie Wang.
Look at the composition.
Look at the camera movement.
I won't look.
Look at me.
Open your eyes.
I won't.
Sister.
Jianshe.
You and the director made me Ning Caichen.
You can't just give up on yourself like this.
That's right, Mr. Heying.
Maybe you can't always be the leading man.
But you can train countless leading men,
just like you did with Jinxi.
Exactly.
What's the point of saying this now?
I can't turn back.
With the long-term contract I signed with King Charlie,
he won't let me go.
Jianshe.
It's fine.
I know someone who deals specifically with King Charlie.
Young Master, I'm just a cleaner.
Don't do this.
A-Tao.
You are a cleaner,
but you not only clean my house,
but also my heart.
I love you.
A-Tao.
I'm the one who truly loves you.
Only I
can give you this wild feeling.
I'm the one who truly loves you.
Choose me.
Choose me, A-Tao.
A-Tao, choose me.
Cut!
Don't you understand human words?
Who yelled 'cut' again?
Why are you here?
I'm here to visit my artist, Du Heying.
Your artist?
Yes.
He signed with me a long time ago.
I was just too busy to check his contract.
Today I found out
that his contract violates labor laws.
Du Heying,
how many hours do you work every day?
About 22 hours.
Is there anyone else here who works more than 22 hours a day?
Excuse me, are you Jin Xi's manager, Sister Hu?
Is your company still recruiting artists?
Why are you joining the fun?
It's none of your business.
Now I
am taking Du Heying away.
Your contract is completely invalid.
If you have any problems,
talk to my company's legal department.
Go.
Didn't you understand?
What are you looking at?
Continue.
You.
You're both the first and second male lead.
As for me,
I will definitely make you famous.
Let's continue on set.
Continue.
Oh my.
That sounds great.
Beautiful.
So amazing.
He sings so well.
As expected of Mr. Heying.
Let's take a 10-minute break.
Director,
everyone,
I'd like to take two minutes of your time.
I want to take this opportunity
to sincerely apologize to everyone.
Actually, my leaving the troupe a while ago,
wasn't because of
my personal health issues,
but rather...
Heying.
We've been working together for so many years,
and you've never taken a single day off.
This time,
just treat it as taking them all at once.
Thank you for helping me persuade Heying to come back.
If you want to thank someone,
thank Xiaoqi.
Xiaoqi?
Your mark is right here.
Okay.
She was the one who found out from Eason
that I went to the studio to look for Brother Jianshe.
So I followed him.
Xiao Qi moved Brother Jianshe with her true feelings.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have come back so quickly.
True.
Xiao Qi has always admired Heying.
I don't think
it's just admiration.
Xiao Qi has feelings
for Brother Jianshe.
Impossible.
We've been working together for so many years.
That doesn't conflict.
No.
She's not that kind of person.
Mr. Heying.
Xiao Qi.
Thank you so much
for spending so much time and effort to persuade me.
It's nothing.
For our theater troupe,
you really...
you really worked so hard.
I feel ashamed.
Mr. Heying,
I might not go this far for anyone else.
But because it's you,
I worked this hard.
I admire your talent,
your aura,
and your dedication to the profession.
I also like you a lot.
So,
I don't want you to give up on musicals,
I don't want you to leave the troupe,
and I definitely don't want to never see you again.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Actually, I also hate to leave everyone.
You...
You should go back first.
Xiaoqi, what did you just say you'd do to me?
Xiaoqi.
Right here.
Where is Jinxi?
Recording a song.
Where is Ningjin?
Rehearsing.
Are you sure no one followed you?
No.
Okay.